现在是二零二二年，天津市初中学业水平考试英语学科听力测试试听部分
Hi, Lingling, what are you doing?
Hi, Peter, I'm reading a storybook.
It's very funny.
Where did you get the book?
I got it from a bookshop.
Really? I just want to buy some books about animals.
I like animals very much.
Where is the bookshop?
It's on Nanjing Road.
I'll take you there.
Thank you. Let's go.
The bookshop on Nanjing Nanjing
It's on Nanjing It's on Nanjing
It's on Nanjing It's on Nanjing Road.
It's It's Nanjing Road.
Hi, Lingling, what are you doing?
Hi, Peter, I'm reading a storybook.
It's very funny.
did you get the book?
I got it from a bookshop.
Really? I just want to buy some books about animals.
like animals very much.
Where is the bookshop?
It's on Nanjing Road.
I'll take you there.
Thank you. Let's go.
视听部分到此结束。
现在是二零二二年，天津市初中学业水平考试英语学科听力测试。
时间，请考生做好准备。
先请听听力测试注意事项：
一，听力理解。
共分三部分内容，从第一小题开始至第二十小题结束。
二，全部听力测试，每部分内容读两遍，请考生边听边答题，
将答案填涂在答题卡上。
现在进行听力理解测试，请考生看试卷的第一页。
of part twice.
一，听力理解。
在下列每小题内，你将听到一个。
或两个句子，并看到供选择的
三幅图画。
找出与你所听句子内容相匹配的图画。
Read twice. 1.
Da Ming didn't find his ruler.
2. You can't touch anything in this museum.
3. The tiger is a large animal and usually lives alone.
The tiger is a large animal and usually lives alone.
4. Tony's sister likes music.
She often buys CDs.
Tony's sister likes music.
下面你将听到十组对话，
每组对话都有一个问题。
根据对话内容，从每组所给的
三个选项中，找出能回答所提问题的最佳选项。
Listen and part test.
Is this your mom, Yes, it is.
6. How often do you go to see a movie, David?
Once a month.
7. often do you go to see a movie, David?
7. There are many clubs in our school.
Which club can you join, I can join the tennis club.
There are many clubs in our school.
8. How old is your little sister?
She is 8 years old.
How old is your little sister?
9. Where shall we meet?
Let's meet in the park.
10. How did you get to
How did you get to the bookshop?
I took a bus.
How to 11.
How long did you stay in Tianjin,
I stayed there for two days.
long did you stay in Tianjin,
Lily? I stayed there for two days.
12. I want to buy this bag.
How much is it?
It's 200 yuan.
Okay, I'll take it.
I want to buy this bag.
How much is it?
It's 200 yuan.
Okay, I'll take it.
13. What are you going to do at the weekend,
I'm going to see my friends.
14. are you going to do at the weekend,
14. What time does Jim's party start?
It starts at 9 o When will you get to his party?
I'll get there half an hour earlier.
16. What time does Jim's party start?
It starts at 9 o When will you get to his party?
I'll get there half an hour earlier.
听下面长对话或独白。
每段长对话或独白后都有几个问题。
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听下面一段材料，回答第十五至第十七题。
嗨，玲玲。
Did you have a good time yesterday?
Yes, I went to the science museum.
Who was with you?
My parents. What did you see in the museum?
I saw many robots.
They were very clever.
What did you do there?
I talked with the robots.
I'd like to go there too.
Hi, Lingling. Did you have a good time yesterday?
Yes, I went to the science museum.
Who was with you?
My parents. did you see in the museum?
I saw many robots.
They were very clever.
What did you do there?
I talked with the robots.
Wonderful! I'd like to go there too.
听下面一段材料，回答第十八至
to What to do at the weekend, Betty?
第二十题。
天津
Lily is going to watch the match with his classmates.
They are going to wear the team shirt.
During the match, they will cheer the players.
It's going to be great fun.
They hope the team will win the match.
They are looking forward to taking photos with the players after the match.
At last, they are going to meet other fans and have a big party.
Tianjin women's volleyball team is Lily's favorite team.
There will be a volleyball match next Sunday.
Lily is going to watch the match with his classmates.
They are going to wear the team shirt.
During the match, they will cheer the players.
It's going to be great fun.
They hope the team will win the match.
They are looking forward to taking photos with the players after the match.
At last, they are going to meet other fans and have a big party.
听力测试结束，请关注紧。
理英语微信公众号。
Thank you for